viewblackporn.com 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy

Last modified on February 5, 2011.  
For definitions and additional information please see the Terms and Conditions.

This document details information regarding the use and disclosure of user data collected on our Website. The security of your data is important and we will attempt to take commercially reasonable steps to limit any risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

We do not provide any facility for sending or receiving private or confidential electronic communications. You should not use this Website or Services to transmit any communication for which you intend only the intended recipient(s) to read. All messages and other content entered into this Website or Services can and may be read by the agents and operators of the Website or Services, regardless of whether they are the intended recipients of such messages.

* ### Data Collected

Users can view content without a username and password, and without any information being collected and processed. However the user�s IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.

A username and password is required for a number of additional features. Personal information may be requested at time of registration, including an email address. Personal information may be added on a voluntary basis after registration. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.

Personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

When you visit our Website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. Our Website uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you delete your persistent cookie, some of our Website�s features may not function properly.

When you visit our Website, our servers may automatically capture information that your web browser sends, including but not limited to: the web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

* ### How Collected Data is Used

Your information submitted to our Website may be used to provide both regular and personalized features.

Your username is displayed to other users alongside the content you upload, including videos and comments. Videos that you submit to our Website may be redistributed throughout the internet, and may be viewable by the public.

We may send you information regarding products or services offered by our affiliates or partners, inform you about any of our related products or services, or provide you with information about any item that we think, in our sole discretion, may be of interest to you.

We may also use your email address for non-marketing or administrative reasons.

We may analyze aggregated user patterns to increase the efficiency of our marketing and hosting operations, and to generally improve the quality of our Website.

* ### When We Disclose Information

If under duty a legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our Website or our subscribers or others, we may disclose your personal data. This includes exchanging information with the police and governmental authorities for any kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms and Conditions. It is our policy, whenever commercially possible and legally permissible, to attempt to notify you of an obligation to supply data to any third party.

Should you upload any allegedly illegal material, we may forward all relevant and available information to all relevant authorities without notice.

The transmission of data via the Internet can never be completely secure. We may use commercially reasonable physical and technical safeguards to preserve the security of your personal data. However, we cannot warrant the security of any data you transmit to our Website and you do so at your own risk.

* ### How We Send Notices

Any notice required to be given under this Agreement may be provided by email to a functioning email address or by a general posting on the Website. You can change the email address to which notice is to be sent at any time. Notices by customers to us shall be given by electronic messages.
